Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Events, 1938-2010; 486103
  - Fundraiser for Brian Steel, 1996; 486164 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - "Future Development of the West Side Waterfront," Presentation by Michael Del Guidice, Oct 1990; 486163 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Holiday Show, 1988; 486162 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Holiday Show, 1989; 486161 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Holiday Show, 1990; 486160 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Holiday Show, 1991; 486159 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Housing Seminar, 1980; 486158 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Insurance Seminar, 1977; 486157 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Luncheon: City Club, Ed Koch Speaking, 1982; 486156 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Luncheon: Construction Industry, 1995; 486155 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Luncheon: Construction Industry, 2005-2010; 486154 (Box 20, Folder 24a)
  - Luncheon: Fall, 1978; 486153 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Luncheon: Fall, 1982; 486152 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Luncheon: Fall, 1988; 486151 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Luncheon: Fall, 1989; 486150 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Luncheon Forum: Agendas, 2000-2007; 486149 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Luncheon Forum: Invitations, 2000-2007; 486148 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Luncheon: General, 1976-1996; 486147 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Luncheon: Governor Malcolm Wilson, 1974; 486146 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1988; 486145 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1989; 486144 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1990; 486143 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1994; 486142 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards (I), 1995; 486141 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards (II), 1995; 486140 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1996; 486139 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, Invitations and Responses, 1996; 486138 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1997; 486137 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1998; 486136 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1999; 486135 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2000; 486134 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2001; 486133 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2002; 486132 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2003; 486131 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2004-2006; 486130 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2008; 486129 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards - Chairman and Guest(s) of Honor List, 1995-2011; 486128 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Luncheon: Seating Lists, 1974; 486127 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Luncheon: Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 1987; 486126 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Luncheon: Speakers List, 1926-1974; 486125 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Luncheon with New York City Department of City Planning, 2008; 486124 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Mayoral Candidates Forum, 1989; 486123 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Outing, Annual, 1978-1981; 486122 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Outing, Annual, 1984; 486121 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Outing, Annual, 1986-1987; 486120 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Outing, Annual, 1988; 486119 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Outing, Annual, 1989; 486118 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Outing, Annual, 1990; 486117 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Outing, Annual, 1991; 486116 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Outing, Annual, 1995; 486115 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Outing, Annual, 1996; 486114 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Outing, Annual, 1998-2001; 486113 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Outing, Annual, 2003-2008; 486112 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Outings: Game Rules, 1961-1981; 486111 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Pension Funds Investment Forum, 1996; 486110 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Reception: General Charles E. Williams, 1989; 486109 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Reception: Holiday, 1994-1996; 486108 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Reception: Joint Real Estate Industry (2nd Annual), 1995; 486107 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Reception: Membership Reception, 2000-2001; 486106 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Reception: Membership Reception, 2007; 486105 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Tour of New York Schools, 1987; 486104 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Series V: Oversized Materials, 1947-2008; 486087 (Box MSXOS002, Folder 1)
  Series V: Oversized Materials, 1947-2008 is comprised of oversized publications, ledgers, and other material.
  - Construction Industry Publicity Program Report, circa 1947; 486102 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Organization Chart (NYBC), 1980-1981; 486101 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - New York Construction News, Jan 14, 1980; 486100 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - New York Construction News: NYBC 65th Anniversary Supplement, May 19, 1986; 486099 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - New York Times: NYBC 50th Anniversary Advertising Supplement, Mar 28, 1971; 486098 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Organization Chart (NYBC), circa 1950s; 486097 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fun and Frolic: "'87 and Beyond or Let's Go B.C.," Sheet Music, Dec 1987; 486096 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Finances: Ledger, Cash Receipts, Jan 1949-May 1951, Apr 1953-Feb 1956; 486095 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Finances: Ledger, Events, 1971-1974; 486094 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Building Congress Update, 1989, 1992; 486093 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - NYBC Update, 1992-2008; 486092 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Haines, Charles: Certificate of Life Membership, Jan 17, 1966; 486091 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Resolutions and Proclamations in Honor of the New York Building Congress, 1991-1992, 1996; 486090 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Design for Certificates of Life Membership and Director Emeritus, Aug 31, 1980; 486089 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Certificate of Service: Stephen F. Voorhees, undated; 486088 (Box MSXOS002, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Photographs, 1936-2008; 485661
  Series VI: Photographs
  The majority of photographic prints in the collection are black and white 8 x 10 prints; also included are color prints in a variety of sizes, including 4" x 6" and 3" x 4". Photographs and matching negatives are placed in the same folder, and the presence of negatives is noted in the finding aid. There are a limited number of contact sheets, also indicated in the finding aid. Additionally, this collection includes approximately 500 stereo slides dating from 1952 and 1953.
  Subseries VI:A: Meetings, 1947-1999, consists of photographs of administrative meetings, including those of the Board of Directors and Council of Presidents, as well as a variety of committees.
  Subseries VI:B: Events, 1944-2008, contains photographs of annual industry and social events, such as the Leadership Awards Luncheon, Fun and Frolic, the Industry Recognition Dinner, and golf outings. Also included are special receptions and forums with prominent visiting speakers.
  Subseries VI:C: Portraits, 1936-1988, includes portraits of key individuals in the building industry and political establishment in New York City. Many of these were acquired for use in NYBC publications, especially for publicity on featured speakers at Congress events.
  Subseries VI:D: Site Photographs, 1948-1974, contains a small number of photographs of construction sites and office environments.
  Subseries VI:E: Other Formats and Oversize, 1943-1988, contains stereo slides produced by the NYBC in 1952 and 1953. The approximately 500 stereo slides document meetings, the annual "Fun and Frolic" (1952 and 1953), and various social outings. Also included in this series are a small number of oversize items and the rolled photographs. Note that approximately 15 tightly rolled photographs, indicated as restricted in the finding aid, are not immediately available for reference use. Please consult Tamiment staff regarding access to these materials.
  - Suberies VI:A: Meetings, 1947-1999; 486012
    - Annual Meeting, May 21, 1952; 486086 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting (Hotel Astoria), May 5, 1998; 486085 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting (Grand Hyatt Hotel): Richard Green: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 20, 1988; 486084 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting (Includes Marilyn Gelber), 1994; 486083 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting: Breakfast Forum: Photos and Negatives, Jan 23, 1998; 486082 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, Jan 1999; 486081 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors; Membership and Building Industry Practices Committees, 1962; 486080 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors (Includes John Dyson), Mar 24, 1998; 486079 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors, Council of Presidents and Foundation Reception, May 1998; 486078 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors (Includes Tony Coles), Mar 24, 1999; 486077 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors: Prints and Negatives, Sep 19, 2000; 486076 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Board of Governors: Cocktail Party, Apr 27, 1949; 486075 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Board of Governors: Meeting: Presentation to Life Members, Mar 28, 1963; 486074 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Board of Governors: Meeting (Includes Marc Shaw and Stephan R.), Apr 1996; 486073 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Board of Governors and Council of Presidents Meeting: Negatives, 1998; 486072 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Board of Governors, undated; 486071 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Capital Needs Assessment Meeting, Dec 11, 1997; 486070 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Committee: Economic Development and Energy: Joint Meeting with Con Edison, Feb 5, 1998; 486069 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Committee: Economic Development; Milos Riverso Forum; Public Buildings Committee: Prints and Negatives, Sep 1998; 486068 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Committee: Transportation: Prints and Negatives, Aug 1997; 486067 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Committee: Energy, Dec 1997; 486066 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Committee: Transportation, 1998; 486065 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Committee: Education, Dec 18, 1998; 486064 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Committee: Membership, Feb 13, 1998; Apr 2, 1998; 486063 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Committee: Public Buildings (Includes Patricia Lancaster), Jan 28, 1998; 486062 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Committee: Public Buildings, Sep 11, 1998; 486061 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Committee: Construction Controls, Dec 5, 1951; 486060 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Council of Presidents: Luncheon, Jun 22, 1983; 486059 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Council of Presidents: Arthur Levitt, Jr. (101 Club): Prints and Contact Sheets, May 20, 1987; 486058 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Council of Presidents: Stephen Berger (101 Club), Jun 6, 1987; 486057 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Council of Presidents (101 Club, Includes Andrew Stern), Sep 23, 1987; 486056 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Council of Presidents (101 Club, Includes Peter Vallone), Oct 21, 1987; 486055 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Council of Presidents (101 Club, Includes Sandy Fruchter), Dec 1987; 486054 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Claire Shulman): Photos and Contact Sheets, Oct 19, 1988; 486053 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Council of Presidents (Grand Hyatt Hotel, Includes Ass. Marc Alan Siegel): Prints and Contact Sheets, Mar 15, 1989; 486052 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Council of Presidents: Luncheon: Contact Sheets, Jan 19, 1994; 486051 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes C. Wisbal): Prints and Negatives, [1994]; 486050 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum with Ruth Messinger: Prints and Negatives, 1995; 486049 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum, 1995; 486048 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum: Prints and Negatives, 1995; 486047 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum with Robert Kiley, 1995; 486046 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Luis Tormenta), Apr 17, 1996; 486045 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Herman Berman): Prints and Negatives, Oct 16, 1996; 486044 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Clay Lifflander), 1996; 486043 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Fran Reiter), 1996; 486042 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Frank Lombardi), Feb 19, 1997; 486041 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Harry Spencer), Apr 15, 1997; 486040 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Council of Presidents, Oct 15, 1997; 486039 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - [Council of Presidents]: Breakfast Forum (Includes Robert Catell), Nov 13, 1997; 486038 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Cathy Nolan): Prints and Negatives, Nov 13, 1997-Nov 19, 1997; 486037 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Colonel Gary Thomas), Dec 17, 1997; 486036 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Council of Presidents: Reception, 1997; 486035 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum (Includes Mark Green and Frederick Ferrer): Prints and Negatives, 1997; 486034 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Brad Race): Prints and Negatives, Mar 20, 1998; 486033 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Joseph Lynch), Apr 15, 1998; 486032 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Kathy Coylde): Prints and Negatives, 1998; 486031 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum (Includes Carl McCall), May 1998; 486030 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Deborah Wright), Feb 18, 1999; 486029 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Robert King), Feb 25, 1999; 486028 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Council of Presidents: Prints and Negatives, Sep 20, 2000; 486027 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Council of Presidents: Prints and Negatives, Oct 18, 2000; 486026 (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Council of Presidents, undated; 486025 (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Formal Acceptance of Wage Stabilization Agreement (Office of the Building Trades Employers' Association), Mar 24, 1948; 486024 (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Public Agency Council [on Transportation]: Prints and Negatives, 1996; 486023 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - Public Agency Council: Capital Needs, undated; 486022 (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Public Agency Council, 1999; 486021 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Staff, Council of Presidents and Economic Development Committee (Includes Robert Boyle), 1997; 486020 (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Unidentified Meeting (Hotel Baltimore), Oct 16, 1950; 486019 (Box 34, Folder 68)
    - Unidentified Meeting, Sep 29, 1955; 486018 (Box 34, Folder 69)
    - Unidentified Meeting, Jul 2, 1969; 486017 (Box 34, Folder 70)
    - Unidentified Meeting, Sep 1976; 486016 (Box 34, Folder 71)
    - Unidentified Meetings, undated; 486015 (Box 34, Folder 72)
    - Unidentified NY Delegation to Washginton D.C., Feb 10, 1947; 486014 (Box 34, Folder 73)
    - Unidentified Presentation, undated; 486013 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Subseries VI:B: Events, 1944-2008; 485719
    - Anniversary Dinner (40th, Hotel Astor): Includes Richard A. Wolff, S.F. Voorhees, John Lowry, James Foley, John F. Hennesey, C. George Dandrow, Alan Horowitz, and Bradford N. Clark, Oct 5, 1961; 486011 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Anniversary (50th), Mar 28, 1971-Mar 31, 1971; 486010 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Anniversary (50th): Conference, Mar 29, 1971- Mar 31, 1971; 486009 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Anniversary (60th), Mar 19, 1982; 486008 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Anniversary (65th): Luncheon (Includes Alfonse D'Amato): Prints and Contact Sheets, May 19, 1986; 486007 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (1), 1997; 486006 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (2), 1997; 486005 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (3), 1997; 486004 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (4), 1997; 486003 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Anniversary (77th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (1), 1998; 486002 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Anniversary (77th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (2), 1998; 486001 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Anniversary (77th): Luncheon Committee Kick-Off Reception: Prints and Negatives, [1998]; 486000 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (1), May 12, 1999; 485999 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (2), May 12, 1999; 485998 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (3), May 12, 1999; 485997 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (4), May 12, 1999; 485996 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (5), May 12, 1999; 485995 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Anniversary (79th): Leadership Awards Luncheon, May 4, 2000; 485994 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Larry Reuter), Apr 19, 1996; 485993 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Sheldon Silver), Feb 27, 1997; 485992 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Breakfast Forum (Alan Hevesi): Prints and Negatives, Jun 1997; 485991 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes John L. Bruno): Prints and Negatives, Dec 18, 1997; 485990 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Joel Miele), 1997; 485989 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Larry Reuter), 1997; 485988 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Joseph Boardman), Feb 19, 1998; 485987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Luis Tormenta), Mar 19, 1998; 485986 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Breakfast Forum (EDC): Prints and Negatives, Feb 23, 1999; 485985 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Rudy Crew), Mar 19, 1999; 485984 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Iris Weinshall): Prints and Negatives, Mar 29, 2001; 485983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - [Breakfast?] Forum, undated; 485982 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Sports Foundation Auction, May 2000 - Jun 2000; 485981 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Building Code: Press Conference, Feb 6, 1961; 485980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Building Code (1963): Signing (Includes Harold Birm, Charles E. Schaffner and Peter Reidy), 485979 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Building Code: Press Conference, 1967; 485978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Building Code: Signing, Nov 6, 1968; 485977 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Business / Labor Breakfast (Sheraton Center, Includes A.L. Delli Bovi), Jan 12, 1989; 485976 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - City Council: Breakfast: Prints and Negatives, Apr 28, 1998; 485975 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - City Council: Reception, Apr 1998; 485974 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Clark, Bradford: Swearing in as Department of Public Works Commissioner, Oct 13, 1963; 485973 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Coletti, Louis J.: Testifying before the U.S. House Subcommittee on Health and the Environment, Aug 3, 1987; 485972 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - C.I.B.D. [Construction Industry Development Board] Summit, 1996; 485971 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Co-op Holiday Party, 1997; 485970 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Dinner: Max Foley Jubilee, May 10, 1949; 485969 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Dinner (Unidentified): Negatives, Jun 1959 (?); 485968 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - [Dinner]: Curtain Call, Dec 1959; 485967 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Dinner: Kick-Off Reception, Sep 1998; 485966 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - [Dinner: Event with Speakers] (1), undated; 485965 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - [Dinner: Event with Speakers] (2), undated; 485964 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Floyd, William: Farewell Party, 1996; 485963 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1944; 485962 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1945; 485961 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 19, 1946; 485960 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1947; 485959 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 21, 1948; 485958 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 20, 1949; 485957 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 19, 1950; 485956 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Fun and Frolic: Rehearsal, Dec 17, 1951; 485955 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1951; 485954 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1952; 485953 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 22, 1953; 485952 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 21, 1954; 485951 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 20, 1955; 485950 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1956; 485949 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1957; 485948 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Fun and Frolic, 1958; 485947 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 15, 1959; 485946 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 15, 1959; 485945 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Fun and Frolic (3), Dec 15, 1959; 485944 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Fun and Frolic, 1960; 485943 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Fun and Frolic, [1961?]; 485942 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 18, 1962; 485941 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 18, 1962; 485940 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Fun and Frolic (3), Dec 18, 1962; 485939 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 17, 1963; 485938 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 17, 1963; 485937 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 15, 1964; 485936 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 14, 1965; 485935 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 21, 1966; 485934 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 21, 1966; 485933 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 21, 1966; 485932 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 13, 1967; 485931 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 13, 1967; 485930 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 11, 1968; 485929 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 11, 1968; 485928 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 18, 1969; 485927 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 18, 1969; 485926 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1970; 485925 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Fun and Frolic: Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 16, 1971; 485924 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Fun and Frolic, 1972; 485923 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 13, 1973; 485922 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Fun and Frolic (2): Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 13, 1973; 485921 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 16, 1974; 485920 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 17, 1975; 485919 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 17, 1975; 485918 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 15, 1976; 485917 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 14, 1977; 485916 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 13, 1978; 485915 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 12, 1979; 485914 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1980; 485913 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1980; 485912 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Fun and Frolic, 1981; 485911 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 15, 1982; 485910 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 15, 1982; 485909 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Fun and Frolic (3): Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 15, 1982; 485908 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 14, 1983; 485907 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Fun and Frolic (2): Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 14, 1983; 485906 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1984; 485905 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1986; 485904 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Fun and Frolic: Prints and Contact Sheets (1), Dec 17, 1986; 485903 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Fun and Frolic: Prints and Contact Sheets (2), Dec 17, 1986; 485902 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 16, 1987; 485901 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), undated; 485900 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), undated; 485899 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Fun and Frolic: Negatives and Contact Sheets, undated; 485898 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - General Events (Identified), 1947-1972, undated; 485897 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Ginsburg, Pam: Birthday Event, Mar 31, 1998; 485896 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Guggenheim Museum Event, Aug 2000; 485895 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Hennessy, John: Party, Aug 20, 1958; 485894 (Box 38, Folder 28)